http://www.cashfiesta.com/php/cf_privacy_infocenter.php

Privacy Policy
News Flash F.A.Q. WebmastersReferral TipsContact UsPoliciesCurrent RatesFiesta CalculatorYour WordsCashfiesta ChecksOnline Games
We Respect Your Privacy
We created this Privacy Policy in order to inform you about the information we collect on
the Cashfiesta.com web site, how we use this information, how we protect it, and what choices
you have regarding the collection and use of your personal information.
Please read the Privacy Policy carefully as by visiting and sharing information on
the Cashfiesta.com site you agree to be bound by the Policy.
Information We Collect
In addition to the information you explicitly share with us when you fill out our join form to become a Cashfiesta.com member, or when you contact us by email or another means, we collect the following information:
Information about your device such as user agent of your browser, the URL that you came to our site from, the IP address you joined or logged in from, join and login timestamps.
If you are logged in, we also collect information about your use of the services we offer, such as offers you respond to.
We collect this information using log files, cookies, and similar tracking technologies.
Cookies
Cookies are small data files that a web site server stores on a computer.
They contain information about activities performed by a user of the computer
on the specific web site and characteristics of the computer at the time the
user navigates the site. Examples: the IP address of the computer at the time
the user navigates the site; the password the user has set for the site,
so that the user doesn't have to type it each time he/she tries to log in at
the site, etc. As cookies are data files, not code, they cannot erase or read
information from a computer's hard drive or from other sites the computer user
visits. Cookies can only be read by the server of the site, which has set them,
so that information about activities on one site can't be transferred through
a cookie to another site.
We may store two types of cookies on your computer:
Session Cookies:
These cookies are stored in the Internet browser and are deleted each time
the browser is closed. We use session cookies mainly to facilitate site
navigation: for example, once you log in to the site, you don't have
to log in again during the same session; and to personalize site experience.
Permanent Cookies:
These cookies are stored on the hard drive of your computer. They are not exactly
"permanent". Each cookie has different "life span" determined by the web site that
sets the cookie. We may use permanent cookies to store your username and password
(encrypted) on your computer if you opt to have it saved.
We may use both types of cookies for aggregate audience analysis: where our visitors
and members come from, which pages they visit, how much time they spend on the site,
which offers are most popular among members, etc. No personal information is stored
in the cookies.
Use of Your information
We use your mailing address and payment info in order to send your payments.
We use your e-mail address to send you our monthly newsletter and other transactional messages related to your Cashfiesta.com membership and,
in case you opt to receive such, special offers and promotions from Cashfiesta.com and on behalf of our affiliated and non-affiliated partners.
We use the tax forms to comply with tax authority requirements.
If you provide us with demographic and interest info, we use it to improve the relevance of the offers we show you.
The information about your activity on the Cashfiesta.com is used to personalize and facilitate your experience, and to prevent abuse.
We also use aggregated, anonymized data to analyze site performance, prevent technical problems, improve existing website services and develop new ones.
We use information about the offers you responded to in order to give you credit for Special Offers you have completed.
We don't create user profiles and don't engage in IBA (interest based advertising) as defined by
NAI
Security of Your Personal Information
Your data may be stored and processed in the United States or the European Union and the European Economic Area in compliance with applicable data privacy and security legislation.
We secure your personal information by using reasonable technical efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of the information that we collect.
We have taken steps to ensure the ongoing integrity, availability, confidentiality and resilience of systems that process personal information,
and will restore information in a timely manner in the event of a technical or physical incident.
Sensitive data exchange between our website and your browser happens over a SSL secured channel and is protected with digital signatures.
Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure.
Although we do our best to protect your data, it may be possible for third parties to unlawfully intercept or access transmitted data.
Unauthorized entry, hardware or software failure, as well as other factors may compromise data security.
We can't guarantee the security of information you transmit to us.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Except as described below, information you provide through the Cashfiesta.com web site
will not be shared with third parties without your permission.
We may share information with third party service providers that perform services on our behalf, such as:
hosting providers, email service providers, payment processors, ad tracking and reporting companies.
These companies can only use the information for the purpose of providing you with the services requested
and provided they comply with all relevant privacy and data security requirements.
Other circumstances under which we may disclose your personal information:
in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
if disclosure is necessary to protect the rights or safety of Cashfiesta.com employees, affiliates, or any third parties
in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or as otherwise required by law;
if Cashfiesta.com or any of its assets are acquired by or merged with another entity.
In such cases we will make sure the acquiring organization agrees to adhere to this Privacy Policy and provides notice in case of changes to the Privacy Policy.
Choice/Opt-Out
If you have opted to receive commercial messages from us and from our partners
and no longer wish to receive those messages, you can opt out of receiving them
by changing your communication preferences in the
Edit Profile section of the site.
However, your option not to receive commercial messages:
(a) shall not preclude us from contacting you, by e-mail or otherwise, regarding your existing or past relationship with us
(e.g. sending you updates about the Cashfiesta.com services, incl. our Monthly Bonus emails), and
(b) shall not preclude us, including our employees, contractors, agents and other representatives,
from accessing and viewing your personal information in the course of maintaining and improving the site.
You can disable cookies in your browser, only allow cookies from selected websites, or select to be notified before accepting cookies.
Note that if you disable cookies, some parts of the websites and other online services you use may not function as expected.
You can also delete cookies stored in your browser at any time. For more information on cookies, see the Cookies part of this Policy.
Personal Information Updates
You can modify or update your personal information after logging in to your Cashfiesta.com account and clicking on the Edit Profile link.
Third Party Websites
This Privacy Policy applies only to the Cashfiesta.com site.
The site contains links that direct you to websites owned and
operated by other companies. In particular, when you take
advantage of an offer, you will be directed to a web site
of our marketing partner that may also collect your personal
information. Those web sites are beyond our control.
You should read those sites' privacy policies before using them.
No Information Collected from Children
In compliance with the
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
Cashfiesta.com will never knowingly collect any personal information about children
under the age of 13. If Cashfiesta.com obtains indication that it has collected
personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be
immediately deleted from our database.
Your California Privacy Rights
Starting January 1, 2006, if you are a California resident, you have the right to receive:
(a) information identifying any third party company (ies) to whom we may have disclosed,
within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for
the company's direct marketing purposes;
and (b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such
information you must make a request in writing. Your request must include your name,
registration email address, and a return address or it will not be processed.
Such requests will not be processed more than once per calendar year.
Requests made via email will not be accepted. Please mail your request to:
Cashfiesta.com/ 41 Sutter St. # 1214/ San Francisco, CA 94104
Your EU/EEA GDPR Rights
Starting May 25, 2017, if you are located in the EU/ EEA, you have the right to access, review, update, correct,
or have your personal information deleted. If you are a registered Cashiesta.com member,
you can access and update most of the personal info we have about you by logging into your account.
For any other privacy related requests, both members and non-members located in the EU/EEA can contact us at
.
We will make commercially reasonable efforts to resolve your issue within 30 days of your request.
If you want your personal information deleted, we will erase all data we have about you.
Please note that we may still use aggregated and de-identified personal information,
and may also retain and use your information if necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, or enforce our agreements.
Privacy Policy Changes
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time.
The new version will be posted on the site. Your continued use
of the Cashfiesta.com site and its products/services represents
your consent to the revised Privacy Policy. It is your responsibility
to periodically revisit the site for possible changes.
Contacting Us
We value your trust and we are committed to your privacy.
If you have any questions about this privacy statement,
Cashfiesta.com practices, or feel that your privacy has been compromised in any way,
© Copyright 2000-20 Cashfiesta.com. All Rights Reserved.
